First, import the new virtual model Hanna from Marvelous Designs and add the default T-shirt to the 3D window.
Since the default clothes and Hanna are all wearing the same clothes, you can directly use the automatic adjustment panel tool to modify the T-shirt.
You can see that the size of the T-shirt has been changed to match the body shape of Hanna.
In order to better check the wearing effect of the clothes, change to A pose.
Since Hanna is wearing high heels, you have to click to keep the current shoes posture.
As the posture changes, the clothing wearing style is also changed.
Next, we are going to make a change to the T-shirt to make it a one-piece lantern sleeve top.
After selecting the line section 3D panel tool, you can draw the line section on the clothes.
Click to create the starting point.
In the process, press the Ctrl key and then click to draw the line section.
The line section is the same as drawing the inner line.
When the 3D line crosses the part between the panel and the model has an intersection or the corner is relatively large, it will not be able to be drawn.
We can double click on the panel to end the creation of the 3D line.
The purpose of drawing the 3D line here is to make a reference for drawing the inner line, which is easy to locate, so you don't have to draw the back again.
Then use the inner line tool to draw the pattern along the 3D line on the clothing.
Note that the starting point and the end point of the inner line must be aligned with the points on the outer line of the panel.
In this way, you can accurately cut the line.
Then select the inner line and select the section in the menu in the menu bar on the right.
Then you can choose the extra panels and delete them.
Since there is no reference to the 3D line in the back panel, we need to change a way, or return the original 3D line and use the 3D line.
For reference, we need to change the way to draw the inner line
Use the tool to edit the line
Select this line that was separated because the panel was deleted
Then select the point at the beginning of the line
Add point
This way, when cutting the back piece
Can ensure that the line is still the same
Based on this point
Draw an inner line
Cut the panel
Delete the unnecessary panel
After simulation, look at the panel
Turn to the back, you will see some penetrations
Currently, the surface diameter of HANA has been reduced to 1
The panel is only attached to the virtual model
But the grid of the panel is too large to penetrate
Reduce the particle diameter of all panels to 15
You can see that the panel is no longer penetrating
In addition, reduce the conflict thickness of the panel
Make the panel more suitable for HANA
Turn to the back, you can see that the panel size is relatively large
So adjust the width of the back
Separately drag the back middle line
This can keep the curve of the sleeve part unchanged
Due to the current pose, the arm is close to the body
So press Shift-X to adjust the skeleton
Adjust the posture
Click on the joint of the arm
Then click on the icon on the upper right of the subscribe ball
Open the symmetrical edit
Change the posture when opening the simulation
In order to prevent the chest panel from moving during the later change of the action
You can use the red dot to fix it on the virtual model
In the bottom of the menu, select the tool to fix the virtual model
Click on the dot on the panel
Then click on the virtual model
After opening the simulation, look at the molding effect
If the position of the panel has formed an obvious deformation
Then you need to adjust it with the edit molding tool
Copy a fabric type and apply it to the large panel
These large panels are the last ones to be applied to the large panel.
After that, it will be made into a natural basic panel
We want to give them a fabric that does not easily stretch and deform
And not easy to fold
After selecting the leather fabric, open the simulation to check the effect
You can see that the fold of the leather fabric is very small
Next, adjust the size to fit
At the same time, select the bottom of the front and back panels and drag the bottom up
In the process, press Shift to move the reference line
Press Alt4 to open the transparency chart
You can check the loose material in the clothing
When using the 3D drawing tool, turn on the transparency display
And draw a line along the body curve as a reference
Use the plus point line tool to add a straight line on the side of the front panel
Add a straight line to the corresponding position on the side of the back panel
After the simulation, check the wearing effect of the outfit again.
Check the side view, you can see that the front is very prominent and the side curves are not right, need to be modified.
Select the point at the bottom of the side to move inside the board.
After the simulation, you can see that due to the changes on the side, the front is more suitable for virtual models.
Change the point in the front to flatten the bottom of the board.
Click on the highest point of the chest, then click on the point in the corresponding position of the bottom of the board, for reference.
Use the plus point division tool to add a point to the bottom of the board.
Then right-click on this point, select Add Render, and enter the corresponding value.
Select a group of lines that form a line, adjust their position to the point of connection between the top and the highest point of the chest.
Then pull up the line point along the vertical direction, lengthen the line and simulate.
After adding a line, the board is more suitable for virtual models.
There are still some inconsistencies on the side, so you need to adjust the line again.
Separate the two points at the bottom of the line, and then pull them apart a little bit.
When they are combined, the board will be more natural.
Of course, only the leather fabric can have such a flat effect, because the bending intensity is relatively high.
If you use default fabric, you will see that there are still some creases.
Change back to the leather fabric and simulate again.
Since the back needs to be made into a skirt, the top is now a bit long.
You can select the bottom and move it up.
But after moving like this, the bottom of the clothes is not flat.
At this time, we can use a tool to cut out the flat bottom.
So let's make the 3D window wider.
Then right-click on the tool bar and click on the clothing measurement tool bar.
After clicking and selecting the long button clothing measurement tool, select the circular measurement and clothing.
Then click on the model near the waist board.
Then use the editor clothing measurement tool to select the green measurement board.
Then right-click and select the bottom of the symmetrical bar.
As you can see, the top one is cut along this measurement board.
Select the excess boards and delete them.
Adjust the straight line point of the bottom board here.
In the process of cutting, one side of the seam allowance will fall, and it needs to be added again.
After checking, we found that the side of the seam allowance has been stretched.
We can use a sewing needle to fix it to the side of the virtual model.
The other side is also operated in the same way.
From the back, the bottom of the bottom is still tight, so we repeat the process.
The bottom of the bottom is still tight, so we repeat the process.
In the case of opening the model, the arm bone is symmetrical.
If it is too open, adjust it again.
As for the base, you can stop when you use all threadchings.
It needs a small chicken always.
Originally, the others in the products were quite big, so we didn't have enough siempre mes to potato salad.
Most products are small, but it doesn't matter.
Sometimes the correlation is not really bad when you sell.
This simple distribute see-through plate is suitable because it right line points.
It is designed to curves the semin need, but it sets the done Houston.
Did you notice?